Jatin Geriya, Technical Research Analyst at Sher Khan,
is with me. Jatin. Good afternoon.
We are currently below 24500, but
we also saw the 2457 level in today's session.
Now, how are the market sentiments
looking from here? How are you reading the strategy and the market?
What will be
your closing trades? Good afternoon. Everybody. So, our
view of Mera Asset Sher Khan Research Team is that
somewhere
we have to look at this market with a stock specific approach.
We feel that in today's trading session
we have seen a perfect example.
Like, the broader market i.e. Nifty is
seeing a little weakness, but the
sectoral index i.e. Bank Nifty and
banking stocks are performing very well.
So, we will look at
this market with a stock specific approach
and considering this is our approach,
we would like to go with a long idea and a short idea. The
long idea will be
in IDFC First Bank. So, a
one-week consolidation on the upside.  There is a breakout towards 69
to 71. We believe that the positive momentum may continue till the levels of 69 to 71. So, it would be
advisable to go long with a stop loss of 64.5 in IDFC
First Bank and the targets would be 69 and 71. The
second recommendation would be towards the sell side.
A negative
divergence is visible in Coromandel on the daily charts.
We believe that going forward,
some weakness may increase in it, so it would be
advisable to sell. The stop loss would be
00 and the target would be
1700. One call is for buying and one call is for
selling. From Jatin's side, Coromandel
International is considering the target of 1700 on the downside. The
opinion is to sell here by maintaining a stop loss of 1800.
Also, among the banking players, there is
buying in IDFC First Bank. The initial target is 69,
after that it can be seen going till 71.
You have to place a stop loss of 50 paise while this stock is trading at the level of 66.  So, one
call was for buying and one was for selling. On behalf of Jatin, we
also have Aditya Arora, Founder and Multiasset Research Alyst of Athletic with us.
Aditya, good afternoon, tell me where is
your focus and how are you tracking the market sentiment? Very
good afternoon to you and to everyone.
See, the market has seen a tremendous rally for so many
days and the important takeaway is that this
reflects the sentiment. Nifty,
small cap, mid cap, many IPOs have seen a
rise at 10, 20, 30, so the market
sentiment has almost shifted from pessimism to optimism
and
24600 is where major call writers are present,
24500 to 600, these are acting as a little resistance for the market,
so
currently the market may take a little pause, but
once 244600 is crossed, this rally
may resume, but
wait for 24600 to be crossed because call writers are
putting pressure here. Due to this
my  A positive outlook is being formed on the insurance sector.
A good correction was being seen in the
insurance sector, but now the
stocks are coming up after forming a base. My pick in this would be
ICICI General Insurance. The stock is making
a good rebound taking support at the moving average of 200,
so you can buy it.
A stock loss will be from 1948 to 49.
From 18777 to 2040, okay, so let's take a
buy call from Aditya. The
first target for ICICI General Insurance is 2017.
After that, targets up to 2040 can also be
seen here and
you have to maintain the stop loss of 18777 here. Lakshmikant Shukla,
Technical Analyst Institutional Research of Yes Securities has
also joined us. Lakshmikant ji,
good afternoon, tell me which spaces are there
on your radar, what stock specific ideas would
you give Lakshmikant ji, please unmute yourself on
Audible. Yes, yes, tell me yes,
hello to everyone, first of all I
would like to tell you that Nifty and Bank Nifty
both have done well.  A bullish head and shoulders
breakout has been observed, and from there, we are
seeing significant upside momentum.
However, the expected targets for
Nifty and Bank Nifty are coming.
Bank Nifty is already sustaining above all its moving
averages, and Bank
Nifty appears to be relatively stronger than
Nifty.
If Nifty is to sustain in the upper range,
I believe that there are
crucial resistances between 24,540 and 24,700.
Once Nifty sustains above 24,700,
a range-bound
rally will continue. We also have good support at lower levels,
visible around 24,100 to 24,000 in June,
where there has been significant put writing.
I believe a short-term
pause is possible. However, the medium-term
bullish outlook for the market will remain as long as
Nifty sustains above 24,000. The
first call I would recommend is
Can Fin Home: I believe the Nifty
financial sector is bottoming out.
I see a
double bottom pattern forming
on the daily charts at Can Fin Home. It reclaimed its 20-day
moving average today.
Both the RSI and MACD are showing positive biases.
I believe we could see significant buying momentum from the current levels.
Our targets for Can Fin Home are
890, and we should maintain a
stop-loss of 815. I would recommend selling the second call
because
I also believe
24,700 is a significant resistance, and the market could
see some profit booking here.
My second call is for Madrasan
Sumi. We should short the December
contract, as I've
seen a breakdown of the rising trend line and rising channel line, along with the
formation of multiple bearish candles. I
believe this stock could see a weakness here.
Expected targets are visible
in Madrasan, they are coming at 156 and we have to
maintain a stop loss of 168, on the upper side
absolute, so one buy call and one
sell call are included, here
targets of 156 are visible on the down side and
apart from this you should maintain a stop loss of 168,
this sell call is
coming at this time and buy calls are also so
clear here, if you see the
market sentiments that are visible on the radar of our experts as well,
we are seeing it in divided form since this morning, there was
short buying for three days but
in today's session the markets have both steadied and fallen
this morning when we were telling you,
see, mixed signals were seen from the foreign market as well,
although the US markets
closed at record levels, but
mixed trading was seen in the Asian market,
if we talk about the start of Gift Ni Nifty, it was
seen happening with sluggishness, the
positioning of FIS is
definitely acting as support for us in the cash market
But apart from this, if you look at there are
many economic indicative action trigger events,
we have already digested some events
like GDP data came and
GST collection came out, the
market is trying to digest these events,
but the credit policy is to come in the coming days, there is a
meeting of OPEC Plus tomorrow and
before this meeting we are seeing that there is a
jump of about 2 per cent in the movement of crude oil, the
decision to increase the production cut may be approved,
some takeaways may come out from there,
so this will also be specially monitored,
apart from this, if we look
at the political scenario also, there was
suspense on the name of the CM of Maharashtra, that suspense seems to be going away now,
so there are clearly many things on
which the market has to react in one way or the other,
although it is also true that
if you look at the levels of the previous expiry,
we had closed at the level of 2387, from there the
market has moved by 600 points, Nifty has
recovered 600 points but from 23350
After crossing the resistance, we
saw 23, 24,500.
After the 24,573 levels, now it is 24,700, which will be the focus.
24,600 is the target, and
if the market maintains the levels there,
then clearly this positive up move will
sustain in the coming days as well. In
a way, we can say that the sure short region will be
clearly noted out.
But for now, if you look at the wallet and this wallet,
you will see that there are sector-
specific PSU banks, realty players, banks,
financials, select
IT players, metals, there is strength here.
And on the contrary, you will see pharma,
FMCG, auto and energy space, which are
facing selling pressure. From a fundamental
perspective, if you look at many
sentiments, there seems to be a boost here
and there are many sentiments
which are also seen impacting real estate and cement to some extent.
Amardev ji, I want to know your opinion on real estate and cement
only.
We are seeing good action in real estate players today.
Nomura released a positive report
on Oberoi Realty. Immediately after that, we
saw good movement in the stock. Just a few days
ago, Jefferies' report on cement came out,
they said that
cement players will
show good performance in the second half of FY25. Realty is the connecting sector.
If we look at today, we can say that
some sectors are involved in managing the market.
How are you seeing the
performance of both the sectors? If we
talk about the real estate sector, then
we will definitely see a lot of growth in the real estate sector in India
over the next three to five years because there are
two or three reasons for this. One reason is
that the interest rate cycle will
remain in our favor and if there is a
rate cut, then it will be a big boost
for the real estate sector. And the second thing is
that all the big real estate players have
somewhere or the other built a good
land back and
now, whether it is the luxury segment or the mid-segment, they are
quite concentrated in these segments and they are
spreading out across the country.
They are getting the benefit of leverage,
and
from a cost implication perspective, and how leveraged they are, that can be a cause
of concern for some of them, but
overall, the next three to five years is a
good time to be in the real estate
stocks story.